Guide to the New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets MSS.559
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Papyri Fragments, 55 Linear Feet in 44 small flat boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1483, cuid32299; 1 fragment 06.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1483)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1484, cuid32300; 1 fragment 04.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1484)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1485, cuid32301; 1 fragment 06.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1485)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1486, cuid32302; 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1486)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1487, cuid32303; 1 fragment 03.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1487)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1488, cuid32304; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1488)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1489, cuid32305; 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1489)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1490, cuid32306; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1490)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1491, cuid32307; 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1491)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1492, cuid32308; 1 fragment 06.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1492)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1493, cuid32309; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1493)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1494, cuid32310; 1 fragment 03.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1494)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1495, cuid32311; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1495)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1496, cuid32312; 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1496)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1497, cuid32313; 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1497)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1498, cuid32314; 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1498)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1499, cuid32315; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1499)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1500, cuid32316; 1 fragment 07.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1500)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1501, cuid32317; 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1501)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1502, cuid32318; 1 fragment 08.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1502)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1503, cuid32319; 1 fragment 09.0 x 09.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1503)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1504, cuid32320; 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1504)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1505, cuid32321; 1 fragment 05.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1505)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1506, cuid32322; 1 fragment 05.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1506)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1507, cuid32323; 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1507)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1508, cuid32324; 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1508)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1509, cuid32325; 1 fragment 06.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1509)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1510, cuid32326; 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1510)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1511, cuid32327; 1 fragment 03.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1511)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1512, cuid32328; 1 fragment 12.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1512)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1513, cuid32329; 1 fragment 05.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1513)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1514, cuid32330; 1 fragment 04.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1514)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1515, cuid32331; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1515)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1516, cuid32332; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1516)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1517, cuid32333; 1 fragment 05.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1517)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1518, cuid32334; 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1518)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1519, cuid32335; 1 fragment 03.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1519)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1520, cuid32336; 1 fragment 06.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1520)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1521, cuid32337; 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1521)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1522, cuid32338; 1 fragment 03.5 x 11.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1522)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1523, cuid32339; 1 fragment 06.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1523)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1524, cuid32340; 1 fragment 06.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1524)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1525, cuid32341; 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1525)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1526, cuid32342; 1 fragment 07.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1526)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1527, cuid32343; 1 fragment 06.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1527)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1528, cuid32344; 1 fragment 09.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1528)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1529, cuid32345; 1 fragment 11.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1529)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1530, cuid32346; 1 fragment 05.5 x 14.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1530)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1531, cuid32347; 1 fragment 00.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1531)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1532, cuid32348; 1 fragment 03.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1532)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1533, cuid32349; 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1533)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1534, cuid32350; 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1534)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1535, cuid32351; 1 fragment 06.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1535)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1536, cuid32352; 1 fragment 09.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1536)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1537, cuid32353; 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1537)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1538, cuid32354; 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1538)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1539, cuid32355; 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1539)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1540, cuid32356; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1540)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1541, cuid32357; 1 fragment 05.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1541)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1542, cuid32358; 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1542)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1543, cuid32359; 1 fragment 05.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1543)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1544, cuid32360; 1 fragment 07.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1544)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1545, cuid32361; 1 fragment 09.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1545)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1546, cuid32362; 1 fragment 08.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1546)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1547, cuid32363; 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1547)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1548, cuid32364; 1 fragment 02.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1548)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1549.01, cuid32365; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1549.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1549.02, cuid32366; 1 fragment 04.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1549.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1550, cuid32367; 1 fragment 11.5 x 12.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1550)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1551, cuid32368; 1 fragment 06.0 x 13.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1551)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1552, cuid32369; 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1552)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1553, cuid32370; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1553)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1554, cuid32371; 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1554)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1555, cuid32372; 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1555)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1556, cuid32373; 1 fragment 08.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1556)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1557, cuid32374; 1 fragment 05.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1557)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1558, cuid32375; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1558)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1559, cuid32376; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1559)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1560, cuid32377; 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1560)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1561, cuid32378; 1 fragment 07.0 x 09.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1561)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1562, cuid32379; 1 fragment 08.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1562)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1563, cuid32380; 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1563)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1564, cuid32381; 1 fragment 06.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1564)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1565, cuid32382; 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1565)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1566, cuid32383; 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1566)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1567, cuid32384; 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1567)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1568, cuid32385; 1 fragment 04.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1568)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1569, cuid32386; 1 fragment 05.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1569)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1570, cuid32387; 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1570)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1571.01, cuid32388; 1 fragment 05.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1571.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1571.02, cuid32389; 1 fragment 11.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1571.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1571.03, cuid32390; 1 fragment 10.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1571.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1572, cuid32391; 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1572)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1573, cuid32392; 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1573)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1574, cuid32393; 1 fragment 05.0 x 14.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1574)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1575, cuid32394; 1 fragment 07.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1575)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1576, cuid32395; 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1576)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1577, cuid32396; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1577)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1578, cuid32397; 1 fragment 03.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1578)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1579, cuid32398; 1 fragment 03.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1579)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1580, cuid32399; 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1580)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1581, cuid32400; 1 fragment 05.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1581)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1582, cuid32401; 1 fragment 04.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1582)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1583, cuid32402; 1 fragment 06.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1583)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1584, cuid32403; 1 fragment 02.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1584)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1585, cuid32404; 1 fragment 07.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1585)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1586, cuid32405; 1 fragment 08.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1586)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1587, cuid32406; 1 fragment 05.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1587)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1588, cuid32407; 1 fragment 04.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1588)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1589, cuid32408; 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1589)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1590, cuid32409; 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1590)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1591, cuid32410; 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1591)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1592, cuid32411; 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1592)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1593, cuid32412; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1593)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1594, cuid32413; 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1594)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1595, cuid32414; 1 fragment 03.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1595)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1596, cuid32415; 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 32, Item P.NYU inv 1596)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1597.01, cuid32416; 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1597.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1597.02, cuid32417; 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1597.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1598, cuid32418; 1 fragment 09.5 x 10.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1598)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1599, cuid32419; 1 fragment 06.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1599)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1600, cuid32420; 1 fragment 05.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1600)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1601, cuid32421; 1 fragment 06.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1601)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1602, cuid32422; 1 fragment 03.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1602)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1603, cuid32423; 1 fragment 08.5 x 17.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1603)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1604, cuid32424; 1 fragment 05.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1604)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1605, cuid32425; 1 fragment 10.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1605)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1606, cuid32426; 1 fragment 07.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1606)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1607, cuid32427; 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1607)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1608, cuid32428; 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1608)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1609, cuid32429; 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1609)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1610, cuid32430; 1 fragment 20.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1610)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1611, cuid32431; 1 fragment 09.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1611)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1612, cuid32432; 1 fragment 05.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1612)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1613, cuid32433; 1 fragment 07.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1613)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1614, cuid32434; 1 fragment 04.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1614)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1615, cuid32435; 1 fragment 07.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1615)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1616, cuid32436; 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1616)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1617, cuid32437; 1 fragment 04.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1617)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1618, cuid32438; 1 fragment 06.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1618)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1619, cuid32439; 1 fragment 06.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1619)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1620, cuid32440; 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1620)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1621, cuid32441; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1621)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1622, cuid32442; 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1622)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1623, cuid32443; 1 fragment 02.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1623)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1624, cuid32444; 1 fragment 03.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1624)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1625, cuid32445; 1 fragment 03.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1625)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1626, cuid32446; 1 fragment 10.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1626)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1627, cuid32447; 1 fragment 02.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1627)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1628, cuid32448; 1 fragment 06.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1628)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1629.01, cuid32449; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1629.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1629.02, cuid32450; 1 fragment 04.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1629.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1630.01, cuid32451; 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1630.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1630.02, cuid32452; 1 fragment 03.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1630.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1631.01, cuid32453; 1 fragment 03.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1631.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1631.02, cuid32454; 1 fragment 03.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1631.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1632, cuid32455; 1 fragment 08.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1632)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1633, cuid32456; 1 fragment 05.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1633)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1634, cuid32457; 1 fragment 09.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1634)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1635, cuid32458; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1635)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1636, cuid32459; 1 fragment 07.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1636)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1637, cuid32460; 1 fragment 06.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1637)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1638, cuid32461; 1 fragment 06.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1638)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1639, cuid32462; 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1639)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1640, cuid32463; 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1640)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1641, cuid32464; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1641)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1642, cuid32465; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1642)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1643, cuid32466; 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1643)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1644, cuid32467; 1 fragment 04.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1644)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1646, cuid32468; 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1646)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1647, cuid32469; 1 fragment 04.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1647)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1648, cuid32470; 1 fragment 03.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1648)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1649, cuid32471; 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1649)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1650, cuid32472; 1 fragment 07.5 x 14.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1650)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1651, cuid32473; 1 fragment 02.5 x 20.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1651)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1652, cuid32474; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1652)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1653, cuid32475; 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1653)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1654.01, cuid32476; 1 fragment 04.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1654.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1654.02, cuid32477; 1 fragment 03.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1654.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1655, cuid32478; 1 fragment 05.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1655)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1656, cuid32479; 1 fragment 04.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1656)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1657, cuid32480; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 33, Item P.NYU inv 1657)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1658, cuid32481; 1 fragment 01.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1658)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1659, cuid32482; 1 fragment 01.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1659)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1660, cuid32483; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1660)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1661, cuid32484; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1661)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1662, cuid32485; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1662)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1663, cuid32486; 1 fragment 00.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1663)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1664, cuid32487; 1 fragment 05.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1664)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1665.01, cuid32488; 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1665.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1665.02, cuid32489; 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1665.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1666, cuid32490; 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1666)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1667, cuid32491; 1 fragment 05.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1667)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1668, cuid32492; 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1668)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1669, cuid32493; 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1669)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1670, cuid32494; 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1670)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1671, cuid32495; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1671)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1672, cuid32496; 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1672)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1673, cuid32497; 1 fragment 04.5 x 00.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1673)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1674, cuid32498; 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1674)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1675, cuid32499; 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1675)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1676, cuid32500; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1676)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1677, cuid32501; 1 fragment 04.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1677)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1678, cuid32502; 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1678)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1679, cuid32503; 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1679)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1680, cuid32504; 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1680)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1682, cuid32505; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1682)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1683, cuid32506; 1 fragment 03.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1683)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1684.01, cuid32507; 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1684.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1684.02, cuid32508; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1684.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1685, cuid32509; 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1685)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1686, cuid32510; 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1686)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1687, cuid32511; 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1687)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1688, cuid32512; 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1688)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1689, cuid32513; 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1689)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1690, cuid32514; 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1690)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1691, cuid32515; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1691)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1692, cuid32516; 1 fragment 07.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1692)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1693, cuid32517; 1 fragment 05.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1693)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1694, cuid32518; 1 fragment 07.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1694)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1695.01, cuid32519; 1 fragment 02.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1695.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1695.02, cuid32520; 1 fragment 01.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1695.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1696, cuid32521; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1696)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1697, cuid32522; 1 fragment 03.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1697)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1698, cuid32523; 1 fragment 07.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 34, Item P.NYU inv 1698)